[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Meat",
    "back": "mięso",
    "phonetic": "/meat/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "front": "Beef",
    "back": "wołowina",
    "phonetic": "/beef/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "front": "Pork",
    "back": "wieprzowina",
    "phonetic": "/pork/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "front": "Chicken",
    "back": "kurczak",
    "phonetic": "/chicken/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "front": "Lamb",
    "back": "jagnięcina",
    "phonetic": "/lamb/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "front": "Fish",
    "back": "ryba",
    "phonetic": "/fish/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "front": "Seafood",
    "back": "owoce morza",
    "phonetic": "/seafood/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "front": "Vegetables",
    "back": "warzywa",
    "phonetic": "/vegetables/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "front": "Fruits",
    "back": "owoce",
    "phonetic": "/fruits/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "front": "Cereals",
    "back": "płatki śniadaniowe",
    "phonetic": "/cereals/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "front": "Bread",
    "back": "chleb",
    "phonetic": "/bread/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "front": "Rice",
    "back": "ryż",
    "phonetic": "/rice/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "front": "Pasta",
    "back": "makaron",
    "phonetic": "/pasta/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "front": "Noodles",
    "back": "kluski",
    "phonetic": "/noodles/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "front": "Cheese",
    "back": "ser",
    "phonetic": "/cheese/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "front": "Yogurt",
    "back": "jogurt",
    "phonetic": "/yogurt/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "front": "Egg",
    "back": "jajko",
    "phonetic": "/egg/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "front": "Salad",
    "back": "sałatka",
    "phonetic": "/salad/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "front": "Soup",
    "back": "zupa",
    "phonetic": "/soup/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "front": "Stew",
    "back": "gulasz",
    "phonetic": "/stew/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "front": "Sandwich",
    "back": "kanapka",
    "phonetic": "/sandwich/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "front": "Pizza",
    "back": "pizza",
    "phonetic": "/pizza/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "front": "Cake",
    "back": "ciasto",
    "phonetic": "/cake/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "front": "Biscuits",
    "back": "ciastka",
    "phonetic": "/biscuits/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "front": "Pastry",
    "back": "ciasto kruche",
    "phonetic": "/pastry/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "front": "Chocolate",
    "back": "czekolada",
    "phonetic": "/chocolate/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "front": "Ice cream",
    "back": "lody",
    "phonetic": "/ice-cream/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "front": "Juice",
    "back": "sok",
    "phonetic": "/juice/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "front": "Tea",
    "back": "herbata",
    "phonetic": "/tea/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "front": "Coffee",
    "back": "kawa",
    "phonetic": "/coffee/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "front": "Water",
    "back": "woda",
    "phonetic": "/water/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "front": "Soft drink",
    "back": "napój bezalkoholowy",
    "phonetic": "/soft-drink/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "front": "Alcohol",
    "back": "alkohol",
    "phonetic": "/alcohol/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "front": "Beer",
    "back": "piwo",
    "phonetic": "/beer/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "front": "Wine",
    "back": "wino",
    "phonetic": "/wine/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "front": "Breakfast",
    "back": "śniadanie",
    "phonetic": "/breakfast/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "front": "Lunch",
    "back": "obiad",
    "phonetic": "/lunch/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "front": "Dinner",
    "back": "kolacja",
    "phonetic": "/dinner/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "front": "Snack",
    "back": "przekąska",
    "phonetic": "/snack/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "front": "Supper",
    "back": "podwieczorek",
    "phonetic": "/supper/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "front": "Dessert",
    "back": "deser",
    "phonetic": "/dessert/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "front": "Appetizer",
    "back": "przystawka",
    "phonetic": "/appetizer/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "front": "Main course",
    "back": "danie główne",
    "phonetic": "/main-course/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "front": "Side dish",
    "back": "dodatek do dania głównego",
    "phonetic": "/side-dish/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "front": "Starter",
    "back": "przystawka",
    "phonetic": "/starter/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "front": "Takeaway",
    "back": "jedzenie na wynos",
    "phonetic": "/takeaway/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "front": "Buffet",
    "back": "bufet",
    "phonetic": "/buffet/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "front": "Catering",
    "back": "catering",
    "phonetic": "/catering/",
    "frontExample": "",
    "backExample": "",
    "remembered": false
  }
]